https://subscription.timeinc.com/storefront/privacy/ew/generic_privacy_new.html?dnp-source=B#california

YOUR PRIVACY
MATTERS
Effective Date: February 12, 2020
Hi we are Meredith! Meredith Corporation and our brands
focus on providing you with destinations you can trust and rely on for every
stage of your life to connect you to great content, products and services and personalize
your experience with us.
Our
mission is to be clear and transparent about how and why we collect and use
information and to empower you to control your personal information. You are
not our product, you are our customer.
When
Does this Policy Apply?
This
Privacy Statement applies when you interact with
National Media Group brands (“Brands”), a division of Meredith
Corporation, through their websites, mobile apps, email communications and
other platforms (our “Sites”)  To
read our EU Privacy Statement click here.
What
Does it Say?
Read
this policy in full, here.
Here are the highlights:
What
Personal Information Do Our Brands Collect about You?
Contact
Information (such
as name, phone number, postal address or email address)
Account/Registration
Information (such
as user name and password, reminder questions and answers and
communications preferences, e.g. signing up for a newsletter or
sweepstake, registering for an offer or an experience, or making a
purchase)
Payment
Information (such
as name, billing address, and credit card information, e.g. when making
a purchase)
Demographic
information
(such as age, gender race, income, occupation, marital status, and
information about your household/family status, including your household
size and the length of time at your residence)
Online
identifiers
(such as IP address, internal and third party identifiers, advertising
identifiers and device information like unique device ID)
Location
Data (like
your address, city, and zip code, collected in limited circumstances)
Internet
Activity Information (such as browsing history, information on how
you interact with our Sites (e.g. which articles or ads you click on,
whether you click on links in our emails), and your interactions with
social media platform features)
Inferences about Your Interests, Preferences and other
Behavioral Data (such as hobbies, and interests (e.g. your favorite
foods, purchases or recipes) and consuming tendencies)
Publicly Available Information
(such as your posts and submissions to blogs, video-sharing services,
and other interactive forums)
MORE
Where/How Do Our Brands Collect
Information About You?
Other Technologies (information
stored on your browser, which tell us your browser, device information, IP
address, and how you interact with the Sites).
MORE
How Do Our Brands Use Your Information?
Our
Brands use your information:
To recognize
you when you are on the Sites to deliver relevant and compelling content
To conduct market
research and analysis to understand general trends (how many readers
do we have? What content is popular? Do people prefer video over
articles?), our Site visitors, how ads perform on our Sites (e.g., who
clicked on the ad?) and how users engage on our Sites (e.g. who read that
article)
MORE
Who Do Our Brands Share Your Information With?
With
Meredith’s other National Media Group Brands, which are covered
by this Privacy Policy.
With
other companies owned by the Meredith Corporation, with
guidelines in place.
With
our service providers, who help operate our Sites and provide our
services to you.
With
the advertisers who advertise on our sites or partner with us to
send you offers, promotions, or ads about products and services that may
interest you.
With
third party data partners who help us identify you and who give
us additional information about you that helps us deliver relevant and
compelling content and services and improve the performance of our Sites.
When
required by law
With
a buyer of all or part of our business.
With
other third parties, when we have your consent.
MORE
How Can You Control Our Use of Your
Information?
You can tell us
how we can use your information by clicking on the links below:
opt-out of postal mail from us, please use the
opt-out form available here.
o
You
can opt-out from any Meredith email newsletter or other email list by using
the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message or by visiting the Email preference
center
(offered by some of our Brands),
We do not
knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 16.
MORE
Rights for Our California Residents
You have all the
rights listed above. In addition, if you’re a resident of California, you
have the right to:
Request
that we not sell your personal information.
If
you would like to exercise this right, click here
Disclose
to you whether we share your information with third parties for their
direct marketing purposes.
Still
can’t find what you’re looking for about our data privacy practices? Don’t
worry, just reach out to us at privacy@meredith.com and we will get back to
you!
What
Personal Information Do Our Brands Collect?
When you visit our Sites, our Brands may collect the following
information from or about you:
§
Online
Identifiers: IP address, advertising ID, unique device ID, and other
information about your device, and internal and third party IDs that have been
assigned to you.
§
Location
Information: Information about your location that you provide us or that we
collect from your device (including city, state, and zip code) (collected in
limited circumstances).
§
Internet
Activity Information: Information about your use of our Sites and other websites you
visit, including the web pages, content and advertisements you view and links
you click on, and whether you open, forward or click the links in emails we
send to you, your browsing history, and social media use including the "shares"
and “likes” you make on a social media platform that is connected to the Sites.
§
Inferences
about Your Interests, Preferences and other Behavioral Data: Hobbies, and interests
(like your exercise and activity levels, your favorite foods, your weight loss
objectives and dietary preferences, which videos you like, your purchases,
favorite recipes, or consumption tendencies).
Some of our Brands offer you the opportunity to sign up for a
newsletter, register on our Sites, or purchase products from us, when you do
that, those Brands may also collect:
§  Contact Information:  Your name, phone
number, postal address or email address.
§
Account/Registration
Information: User name and password, reminder questions and answers,
subscription and account numbers, and communications preferences (such as which
newsletters you would like to receive).
§
Payment
Information: Billing address, shipping address, credit card or bank account
number, expiration date, and card verification number (when you provide that
information to us).
§
Demographic
Information: Age, gender, race, education level, income information, occupation,
marital status, and information about your household/family status such as the
presence of children/child age ranges, household size, own/rent indicator, and the
length of time at your residence.
Where/How Do We Collect Information About You?
We
collect information about you from a number of sources:
From you.  Some of our Brands collect your contact, registration/account
information, and payment information and any other information when you provide
it to us on the Sites.  When you make a purchase on the Sites, we also retain a
record of your purchases and order history.
From your Device.
What are Cookies & Other Technologies?
§
Cookies.
A
“cookie” is a tiny file that’s stored on your computer. It contains a unique
identifier, as well as the address and other information about the website you
are visiting.  Cookies help us know whether you are a returning visitor to our
Sites.  For example, although you may not log-in when you visit our Sites, we can
use cookies to recognize that you have visited the Site in the past. By using
cookies, we are able to understand what is of interest to our customers and
ensure the content and services we offer are relevant and compelling when you
visit our Sites.  In some cases, we may use the information we collect from
cookies, to deliver relevant and compelling content to you when you visit the Sites.
§
Web
Beacons, Pixel Tags and Other Tracking Technologies.  Web beacons, pixel techs
and other “tracking technologies” are small strings of code placed on a web
page or in an email or advertisement.  These technologies allow your browser to
recognize and store certain types of information such as cookies previously
set, the time and date that you viewed the page with the beacon and a
description of that page.
Can You Opt Out?
In
most cases, yes!  There are some cookies that we need in order to operate the
Sites.  If you deleted those cookies, the Sites would no longer function (as an
example, if we can’t remember the items you put in a shopping cart, then you
won’t be able to place an order on the Sites).  You can always decide to
opt-out of or delete the third party cookies (cookies set by Advertisers and
Data Partners) on our Sites.  Keep in mind, if you block cookies, you may not
be able to view or access some of the features of our Sites.  Visit our section
on your privacy choices for more information on
how to opt-out.
From Others.
§  Advertisers.  In some cases, the
Advertisers who serve ads on our Sites will share your email or online
identifiers with us so that we can make sure their advertisements or offers
reach you.
§  Data Partners.  We work with third party
data partners who share information with us about your demographic information,
internet activity information, purchasing information, and your interests,
preferences, and other behavioral data, which help us understand you better and
ensure the content and services we offer are relevant and compelling.
§  Service Providers. We work with service
providers who collect information on our behalf in order to provide services to
us, such as hosting our websites, processing our credit card transactions,
fulfilling your subscriptions and orders, verifying your identity, and other activities
needed to help us provide our content and services to you.  We only allow our
service providers to use your personal information in connection with the
services they provide us.
How Do We Use Your Information?
We and our
other
Meredith Companies and the Service Providers working on our behalf use information collected
about you to:
To Contact You
§  To send you emails,
including our Brand newsletters, surveys and other communications.
Fulfill Your Subscriptions, Orders and Other Requests
§  Fulfill your orders and
requests for products, services, and information (including to send you email
or other newsletters).
§  Some of our brands offer
products and services you can purchase individually or on a subscription basis.
We use the information you provide at check-out to process your orders on those
sites.
Create and Manage your Account
§  Create and manage your Account,
including providing you with access to your Account.
Marketing Meredith to You
§  We may use your
information to market the Meredith’s Brands to you, as well as the products and
services of the other companies owned by Meredith.
Personalize Your Experience on Our Sites, Including the Content
and Ads Displayed to You
§  Customize the content and
ads you see when you use our Sites, third party sites, and in our email
communications.
§  Remember your browser
settings and any preferences you set while using the Sites.
§  Recognize you across our
Sites so that we may deliver relevant interest-based content and advertising to
you.
Provide and Improve the Sites
§  Analyze, operate and
improve our Sites (including repairing errors or debugging) or develop new ones.
§  Allow you to participate
in features such as surveys, polls, sweepstakes, and message boards.
§  Measure and analyze
visitor traffic and usage patterns and improve the quality and effectiveness of
our Sites, features and related communications.
Advertising, Marketing and other Research for our Advertisers
§  Provide you with special
offers, promotions and information from the Meredith companies, and select
third parties (as permitted by law).
§  To understand trends in
how the visitors to our Sites interact with the ads, content, and features on
our Sites (e.g. your behavior on our Sites may be included in a general report
about whether people prefer video content over written content on our Sites).
§  Help our Advertisers
reach you by email.
§  Conduct market or
audience analysis and related reporting (e.g. to give reports on who our
visitors are and whether the ads displayed are effective).
Security and Fraud Prevention
§  Enforce our legal rights
or comply with the law.
§  Prevent potentially
prohibited or illegal activities, comply with applicable law and enforce our see the terms of service on the applicable
website.
We may use your
information for any other purposes disclosed to you at the time we collect your
information, provided we have obtained the required consent.
Who Do We Share Your Information With?
We may share your personal information with our other Meredith Companies,
Service Providers, Social Media Platforms, Advertisers, and Third Party
Data Partners.
§  Meredith Companies.  The Meredith
Brands covered by this Privacy Statement share your personal information with
each other, and will use that information as described in this Privacy
Statement.  Our Brands also share your personal information with other companies
in the Meredith family, which have their own privacy
statements and are not subject to this Privacy Statement.
§  Service Providers.  We engage Service
Providers to provide services such as credit-card and billing processing,
shipping, marketing, advertising optimization and interest-based targeting,
email and text message distribution, data processing, mobile and website
analytics, user authentication, security and promotions management.  We may
share any information we collect about you with these Service Providers and
authorize them to collect information from you directly to support the services
they provide to us.  We do not authorize our Service Providers to share or use your
information with any other third parties.
§  Social Media Platforms.  To make your experience
with our Sites more enjoyable, we may offer features made available by social
media platforms (such as likes or social sharing).  Some social media platforms
may collect information directly from you pursuant to their own separate
privacy policies which may differ from ours. Some social media platforms also act
as our data partners, which means that we may share your personal information
with them as described below under “Data Partners.”
§
Advertisers.
We are
able to provide most of our Sites and other content to you for free with the
help of the Advertisers who promote their products and services on our Sites.  Brands
with ad-supported Sites share aggregate visitor information with Advertisers,
which includes information about your demographics, Internet activity
information, interests and preferences. In some cases, we share contact
information (such as your name, age, and/or email address) or online
identifiers with these Advertisers.  If you sign up for a special email offer
from one of our Advertisers, our Brands will also share your email address and
any other information you provided with your request with the advertisers you
selected.
§
Data
Partners. Some
of our Brands provide select third party Data Partners with lists of our user
email addresses in a hashed, encrypted or anonymized form that they use to
recognize you.  These Data Partners will provide us with additional information
about you (such as your interests, preferences or demographic information).  Other
Data Partners use cookies and other tracking technologies to enable the
delivery of interest-based advertising to users. We do not authorize our Data
Partners to share your email address with their other clients.
§
Legal
Compliance, Business Transfers, and Other Disclosures.  We disclose information
about users of our Sites when we believe the law requires it. For example, to
respond to compulsory process or law enforcement requests, to enforce our terms of service for relevant brands, or to protect the rights,
property or safety of users, the public, Meredith Companies, Service Providers,
Social Media Platforms, Advertisers, Data Partners, or third parties.  Over
time, we may reorganize or transfer various assets and lines of business. We
reserve the right to disclose or transfer any information we collect to third
parties in connection with any proposed or actual purchase, sale, lease,
merger, foreclosure, liquidation, amalgamation or any other type of
acquisition, disposal, transfer, conveyance or financing of all or any portion
of Meredith companies.
How Can You Control
Our Use of Your Information?
What
Rights Do You Have?
§  Right to Know: You have the right
to ask us to tell you what personal information we collect use, disclose and
sell about you.
§  Right to Request
Deletion: You
have the right to ask us to delete the personal information we collect or
maintain about you.
§  Right to be Free from
Discrimination: You
have the right not to be discriminated against for exercising these rights.
§  Right to Access or
Correct Your Information: You have the right to request access to and to edit
certain personal information that you have provided to us through our Sites.
We are only legally required to honor these rights
in certain jurisdictions, but, we are working towards honoring these rights for
all Meredith visitors.  If you are in the U.S. and wish to exercise your
rights:
§  Information and
Deletion Requests. To
exercise your right to for information on our data collection practices on this
Site or request deletion of the information on this Site, please use the
request form available here We will need to verify that you are who you
say you are before we delete or share personal information with you.  After you
submit your request, you will be sent a confirmation email and need to click on
the link provided. If you are a postal subscriber, we may need to request more
information from you in order to verify your request.
What Other
Choices Do You Have?
Marketing
Communications
Postal
Mail. To
remove your name and postal address from lists that we sell or rent to third
parties for their direct marketing purposes, or to opt-out of receiving marketing offers for other Meredith
magazines and products by mail, please use the opt-out form available here or send your request
to us in a letter addressed to Meredith Corporation, Opt-Out Postal, Attn: Circulation, 1716 Locust
Street, Des Moines, Iowa 50309.
Note
that if you choose to opt-out of Meredith’s promotional mailings, you may still
receive renewal notices and related offers for any magazines to which you
subscribe.
Email.
You can
opt-out from any Meredith email newsletter or other email list by using the
unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message or by visiting Email Preferences (offered by some of our
Brands) on our Sites and updating your preferences. If you no longer want to
receive third party email offers that you requested through our Sites, simply
follow the advertiser's unsubscribe link or opt-out instructions that should be
included in every commercial message you receive.
Opt-Out of Cookies & Other
Technologies.
There are a few ways to opt-out or delete cookies:
On your browser (Chrome, Safari, etc.).  The settings of the
browser you use give you an option to accept or reject most cookies, or to
notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the
"Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie
preferences.) Please be aware that certain browsers cannot block or delete
so-called "Flash" cookies, which use a feature of the Adobe Flash
video player to store information on your computer. For information about
how to delete Flash cookies, please visit the Adobe website This will opt you out
of cookies on the browser you are using. If you use multiple browsers, you will
need to take this step for all relevant browsers.  Please note that denying all or certain cookies may result in a
less personalized experience of some of the services offered on the website.
Opt-Out on a Mobile Device. Depending on your device and operating
system, you may be able to reset your mobile device's advertising identifier to
limit this data collection or prevent the collection of usage data across
unaffiliated applications for interest-based advertising purposes by accessing
the privacy settings on your mobile device. Each operating system, iOS for
Apple devices, Android for Android devices and Windows for Microsoft devices,
provides its own instructions. Visit the privacy settings for your mobile
device or contact your platform operator for more information.
Opt-Out
of Nielsen’s Tracking Technologies.  Some of our Advertisers and Brands may use Nielsen’s
measurement services, which contribute to market research, like Nielsen’s TV
and Online Campaign Ratings service.  Nielsen’s pixel may be in some of the ads
on our Sites and will record whether or not you viewed the ad.  Nielsen uses
the data it collects to create ratings reports for advertisers and publishers.
For more information about Nielsen's information collection practices and any
related opt-out choices, please see the Nielsen.com privacy policy.
Opt-Out of Interest-Based Advertising
We
follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s ("DAA") Self-Regulatory
Principles for Online Behavioral advertising.
§  To opt-out of our use of
your website viewing data to serve interest-based advertising on third party
websites and email newsletters, visit the DAA’s Consumer
Choice Page
§  You can also click on the
Ad Choices located in the footer of our websites and navigate to the consumer
opt-out form.
§  Most of the third party
advertising and data companies we work with, including DoubleClick and Google
also subscribe to the DAA Principles and/or are members of the Network
Advertising Initiative ("NAI"). To learn more about the information
collection practices of NAI members and your related opt-out choices, please
visit the NAI's
website.
§
You
must opt-out separately from each computer or device and browser that you use
to access our Sites and if you clear your cookies, you will need to repeat the
opt-out process.
**Note
that many of our websites allow you to adjust your cookie preferences. You can
find these controls in the footer of our websites.
Mobile App Advertising and Tracking
Some of our brands may collect information about your mobile
device, including unique advertising identifiers and the names and IDs of apps
you have installed, as well as information about how you use our mobile
applications and other unaffiliated applications. We and our partners use this
information to enable interest-based advertising you receive through our Sites
and within third party apps and other marketing channels.
For information about the mobile data collection practices of
the service providers we use to support interest-based advertising in our
AllRecipes mobile applications and your additional opt-out choices, click here and here.
Do Not Track
We do not currently respond to browser
do-not-track signals. Instead, we adhere to the standards set out in this Privacy
Statement and offer the opt-out choices described above.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 16 to provide us
with any personal information online. Children should always get permission
from their parents before sharing any personal information about themselves
over the Internet. If you're under 16, please do not register for the Sites or
provide us with any personal information.
Additional
Privacy Information
§
Contests and Other Co-Sponsored Promotions.  From time to time, we may
offer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions. Participation in these
promotions may require registration on our Sites.  We may share your
registration information with co-sponsors or other third parties involved in
the promotion that we identify in the rules or entry materials. We don't
control these third parties' privacy practices, and our Privacy Statement does
not apply to their collection and use of your information. We may also share
some of your entry information with third parties or the public in connection
with the administration of the promotion, such as winner selection and prize
fulfillment, and as permitted by the promotion's official rules, such as on a
winners' list.
§
Security, Retention and Storage of Information.  We use commercially
reasonable procedures to protect the information that we collect. However, we
cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that
information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over
the Internet. Please see our terms of service for the relevant brand for more information related to posting
materials on our Sites including our use of such materials.
§
Location of Your Data.  Meredith is a U.S. company and your personal information will be transferred
to, processed, stored and accessed by us, the Meredith Companies and Service
Providers in the United States and in other jurisdictions where we or they
operate, which may not provide you with the same level of privacy protection as
you are entitled to in your jurisdiction.
§  EU-U.S.
Privacy Shield.  Meredith adheres to the principles of the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield
Framework (“Privacy Shield Principles”) as set forth by the U.S. Department of
Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information
transferred from the European Union (“EU”) to the United States, and it is in
the process of certifying its compliance with the U.S. Department of Commerce.
If there is any conflict between the terms in this Privacy Policy and the
Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles will govern.  To learn
more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit the Privacy Shield website.
Meredith is responsible for the processing of personal information
it receives under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework, or subsequently
transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Meredith complies
with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers from the EU and
EEA, including onward transfer liability provisions.
The U.S. Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over Meredith’s
compliance with its obligations under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield.  In certain
situations, Meredith may be required to disclose personal information in response
to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security
or law enforcement requirements.
In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Meredith commits
to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal
information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy
Shield policy should first contact us at privacy@meredith.com If you do not receive
timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved
your complaint, you may submit your complaint at no cost to you to JAMS, our independent recourse mechanism, at https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield. In the event there are residual complaints that have not been resolved by JAMS, or any other means, you may seek a non-monetary remedy through binding arbitration to be provided to you in accordance with the Privacy Shield Principles.
§  Changes
to Our Privacy Policy.  Digital technology is rapidly evolving. If we decide to change our
Privacy Statement in the future, we'll post the changes here and indicate at
the top of the policy the last date on which it was updated. Unless otherwise
noted, all changes will be effective when posted.
Rights for Our California Residents
This section contains information on the personal information we
collect about residents of California (our “California Consumers”), including
the sources of that information, how that informed is used, who it is shared
with, and the rights that California Consumers have under California law. Our
collection of your information, our data sharing practices, and your privacy
rights are discussed below.
I.
Our Collection of Your Information
What Information Do We Collect About You?
Where Do We Collect this Information From?
Why Do We Collect this Information?
Who Do We Share this Information With?
Contact Information (Name, Email,
Postal Address, Zip Code, Telephone Number)
§ From you when you register
on our sites, subscribe to one of our publications, or otherwise submit this
information to us.
§ From our
Advertisers
who place ads on Services.
§ From our Data Partners (these are
companies who give us information about you to help us and our Advertisers
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§  To contact you (to deliver our
newsletters, surveys, and other communications to you).
§  To fulfill your
subscriptions,
orders and other requests.
§  To market our
Services to you.
§  To create and
manage your account
when you register on our Services, and provide you with your membership
benefits.
§  To combine with
other information we receive from our Data Partners to help us learn more
about you, your interests and preferences so that we can customize your
experience on our Services (including the content and advertisements
displayed to you).
§  To deliver targeted
advertisements
to you on social media platforms or other third party websites.
§  To help our
Advertisers contact you.
§  To help us
measure the effectiveness of the ads on our Services, including to
understand whether you click on the ads on our Services and whether you buy
the products/services advertised.
§  To prevent fraud,
including verifying your identity
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to provide services to us, including
advertising, website support, analytics, payment processing,
subscription/order fulfillment and customer service).
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who we share personal information with to help us identify
potential customers, and to understand who you are and what you may be
interested in).
§ Our Advertisers (the brands that
advertise on our Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
§ Social Media Platforms.
§ Other Meredith Brands and
Companies.
Account/Registration
Information (Name, username, and password)
§ From You when you create an
account or register on our Services.
§To create and
manage your account
when you register on our Services, and provide you with your membership
benefits.
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to provide services to us, including
advertising, website support, analytics, subscription/order fulfillment and
customer service).
Demographic
Information
(age, race, gender)
§ From You when you share that
information with us on surveys, registration or other forms on our Services.
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who give us information about you to help us and our Advertisers
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ To create consumer
segments
(groups of cookies and other IDs based on information we collect about, for
example “Women age 35-44 who have purchased mascara.”, which we share with
advertisers looking to sell mascara or products we think people who like
mascara may also be interested in).
§ To serve targeted
ads to you
(to help us, our advertisers, and our advertising networks and platforms to
identity the best ads to display to you on our Services, based on the
Interests, Preferences and Other Behavioral Data associated with your online
identifiers).
§ To help us identify
you and understand your interests and preferences so that we can customize
your experience on our Services (including the content and advertisements
displayed to you).
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to provide services to us, including
advertising, website support, analytics, subscription/order fulfillment and
customer service).
§ Our Advertisers (the brands that
advertise on our Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
§ Other Meredith Brands and Companies.
Online Identifiers (IP addresses,
device IDs, and other internal and third party identifiers we use to
recognize you online)
§ From Pixels, Cookies, and Other
Tracking Technologies, which collect information about you when you visit
our Services online.
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who give us information about you to help us and our Advertisers
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ To create consumer
segments
(groups of cookies and other IDs based on information we collect about, for
example “Women age 35-44 who have purchased mascara.”, which we share with
advertisers looking to sell mascara or products we think people who like
mascara may also be interested in).
§ To serve targeted
ads to you
(to help us, our advertisers, and our advertising networks and platforms to
identity the best ads to display to you on our Services, based on the
Interests, Preferences and Other Behavioral Data associated with your online
identifiers).
§ To help us measure the
effectiveness of the ads on our Services, including to understand whether
you click on the ads on our Services and whether you buy the
products/services advertised.
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to provide services to us, including
advertising, website support, analytics).
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who we share personal information with to help us identify
potential customers, and to understand who you are and what you may be
interested in).
§ Our Advertisers (the brands that
advertise on our Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
§ Other Meredith Brands and Companies.
Online activity
information
(browsing history, search history, information about your interactions with
our Services)
§ From Pixels, Cookies, and Other
Tracking Technologies, which collect information about you when you visit
our Services online.
§  Data Partners (these are
companies who give us information about you to help us and our Advertisers
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ To create consumer
segments
(groups of cookies and other IDs based on information we collect about, for
example “Women age 35-44 who have purchased mascara.”, which we share with
advertisers looking to sell mascara or products we think people who like
mascara may also be interested in).
§ To serve targeted
ads to you
(to help us, our advertisers, and our advertising networks and platforms to
identity the best ads to display to you on our Services, based on the
Interests, Preferences and Other Behavioral Data and Online Activity
associated with your online identifiers).
§ To help us measure the
effectiveness of the ads on our Services, including to understand whether
you click on the ads on our Services and whether you buy the
products/services advertised.
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to provide services to us, including
advertising, website support, analytics).
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who we share personal information with to help us identify
potential customers, and to understand who you are and what you may be
interested in).
§ Our Advertisers (the brands that
advertise on our Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
Other Meredith
Brands and Companies.
Payment Information
§ From you when your place an order on
our Services.
§  To fulfill your
subscriptions
and orders, and any refund requests.
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to process your payments on our behalf).
Interests,
Preferences and other Behavioral Data (including purchase behaviors)
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who give us information about you to help us and our Advertisers
understand who you are and what you may be interested in).
§ From Pixels, Cookies, and Other
Tracking Technologies, which collect information about you when you visit
our Services online.
§ To create consumer
segments
(groups of cookies and other IDs based on information we collect about, for
example “Women age 35-44 who have purchased mascara.”, which we share with
advertisers looking to sell mascara or products we think people who like
mascara may also be interested in).
§ Service Providers (companies who use
your personal information solely to provide services to us, including
advertising, website support, analytics).
§ Data Partners (these are
companies who we share personal information with to help us identify
potential customers, and to understand who you are and what you may be
interested in).
§ Our Advertisers (the brands that
advertise on our Services and provide offers and other promotions to you).
Other Meredith Brands and Companies.
II.
Our Data Sharing Practices
We share the
personal information below with our Service Providers. Our Service Providers
help us send our newsletters to you, fulfill your orders, provide advertising
and marketing services, and analytics, and other activities that support our
business Service Providers only use the personal information we share with them
to provide these services to us.
Below are the
categories of personal information we disclose to our Service Providers:
some limited circumstances, some of our Brands share your personal information
with third parties who we allow to use that information for their own
commercial purposes.
Below
are the categories of personal information that some of our Brands sell to third
parties:
Interests,
Preferences and other Behavioral Data
III.
Your Privacy Rights
What Rights Do You Have?
§  Shine the Light
Rights –
You have the right to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of
charge, a list of the third parties to whom we have disclosed certain types of
personal information (if any) for their direct marketing purposes in the prior
calendar year. At our option, we may respond to such requests by providing
instructions about how our users can exercise their options to prevent our
disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing
purposes.
§
Right
to Opt-Out of a Sale of Personal Information – You have the right to ask
us not to sell your information to third parties.
IV.      How Do You
Submit These Requests to Us?
In addition to the
rights detailed in the “How Can You Control Our Use of Your
Information?”
section above, California residents can:
§  Contact us to
exercise your Shine the Light Rights at privacy@meredith.com.
§  Opt-Out
of Sales. To opt-out of the sale of your personal information on this
questions or concerns about the Meredith Corporation. Privacy Statement or its
implementation please contact us via email by clicking here or by writing to:
